https://www.directgolfholidays.com/privacy-policy/

Home Privacy Policy
Name *Email *TelephoneArrival Date *Choose Destination *Please ChooseSpain - AlmeriaSpain - Costa BlancaSpain - Costa BravaSpain - Costa de la LuzSpain - Costa del SolSpain - MadridSpain - MallorcaSpain - MurciaSpain - SevillaSpain - TenerifePortugal - AlgarvePortugal - LisbonMorocco - MarrakechMorocco - AgadirTurkey - BelekBulgaria - Black SeaNumber of Nights *Number of Golfers *Number of Non-GolfersNumber of Rounds *Accommodation preferenceNo PreferenceHotel 3 ***Hotel 4 ****Hotel 5 *****ApartmentsGolf ResortNot RequiredTransportNot RequiredCar HireTransfersWhere did you hear about us?Please ChooseInternet searchNewsletterExisting customerWord of mouthOtherAdd your detailed requirements hereURLGDPR Agreement *I consent to having this website store my submitted information so they can respond to my enquiry. *PhoneSubmit
Direct Golf Holidays operate in accordance to EU Privacy Laws!
The privacy of your personally identifiable information is very important to us. As part of our commitment to the privacy of your personally identifiable information, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information is requested.
The privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this site, www.directgolfholidays.com only. Other Web-sites we provide links to may have different practices. If you follow a link to, or otherwise visit these or any other Web sites, please review the privacy policies posted on those sites.
In general, when you visit our site www.directgolfholidays.com you remain anonymous, but, on some pages, you need to provide personally identifiable information in order to register or contact Us. The types of personally identifiable information collected at these pages may include Name, Company, Customer Number (if applicable), Address, E-mail, Address, Phone Number, Fax Number. We regard all these fields as personal information and as such treat them with confidentiality.
We would like to inform you that in compliance with current legal EU regulations regarding Data Protection of personal details, your personal information will properly recorded in the Register of the Agency for Data Protection and that such personal information will be treated confidentially.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide to communicate with you, for example, to answer the e-mail and correspondence we receive. We may use your information to make recommendations for products or special offers, and to provide you with updates on new products that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive this information in the future, please contact our web team at info@directgolfholidays.com
From time to time, we may share certain information with select third parties in order to fulfill your requests or to offer products or services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your information, please contact us at info@directgolfholidays.com
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency’s request.
We will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such uses.
Customization and Aggregate data
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and gather information for product management and development. For example, we may tell our marketing staff that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website during a particular time period, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. This aggregate information may also be shared with distributors or dealers.
Cookies – VERY IMPORTANT INFORMATION
When you view our website (or the website of one of our advitisers) we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” and will help us better serve you. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. Cookies cannot contain virus or harmful program code. It does not require large space on your hard drive and can be deleted.
This information allows us to measure site activity and to tailor information to suit your individual preferences, for example subscription of news. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit. By showing how and when our visitors use this web site, this information can help us to improve our web site on a continual basis. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, please see the help files of your browser to learn how to do this.
First Party Cookies
These are cookies that are set by this website directly.
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.
You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at:
http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html
Our websites runs the popular Concrete5 CMS and cookies are used to store basic data on your interactions with our site, and whether you have logged into our services. We use a session cookie to remember your log-in for you if you are a registered user and we deem these as being strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled then various functionality on the site will be broken.
More information on session cookies and what they are used for at http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/session-cookies-used-for.html
Third Party Cookies
These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by **LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook, Google+ and Pinterest. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.
You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.
Changes to the Policy
Our privacy practices, like the online medium itself, are subject to change. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement at our site.
Third Party links.
Some of the features on our website may be provided by third party services, these services are hosted on websites other than ours. The user should read the terms and conditions of these websites and check the privacy policy of that site, before using. We are not responsible for the privacy policy of our advertisers.
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies or wish to have your personally identifiable information deleted from our records, please send an email to:
info@directgolfholidays.com
We thank you for taking the time to read this important information.
REQUEST A CALLBACK we will be in touch
Name *Telephone *NameSend Request
Name *Email *TelephoneArrival Date *Choose Destination *Please ChooseSpain - AlmeriaSpain - Costa BlancaSpain - Costa BravaSpain - Costa de la LuzSpain - Costa del SolSpain - MadridSpain - MallorcaSpain - MurciaSpain - SevillaSpain - TenerifePortugal - AlgarvePortugal - LisbonMorocco - MarrakechMorocco - AgadirTurkey - BelekBulgaria - Black SeaNumber of Nights *Number of Golfers *Number of Non-GolfersNumber of Rounds *Accommodation preferenceNo PreferenceHotel 3 ***Hotel 4 ****Hotel 5 *****ApartmentsGolf ResortNot RequiredTransportNot RequiredCar HireTransfersWhere did you hear about us?Please ChooseInternet searchNewsletterExisting customerWord of mouthOtherAdd your detailed requirements hereURLGDPR Agreement *I consent to having this website store my submitted information so they can respond to my enquiry. *WebsiteSubmit
